hummaa.com 2014-06-30

# Privacy | Hummaa

## Privacy policy

**hummaa.com, (EFFECTIVE AS OF JANUARY 1, 2007)**

**PLEASE READ CAREFULLY.**  
We recognize the importance of protecting your privacy and our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us, and to assist you in making informed decisions when using the Site. This Privacy Policy will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers' needs. As we update and diversify our services, this Privacy Policy may evolve. Please check this page for updates periodically. We will try to post any changes to this Privacy Policy before they become effective. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here, by email or by means of a notice on our Site's home page that you must view to access the Service.

Please note: By using or registering with our Site or by providing personal information, you agree to abide by these terms.

We have several areas where you can submit information to us, and we also have features that automatically collect information from the users of our Service and visitors to our Site. 

**INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO US.** We have certain areas where we ask you to provide information to us: 

* Registration. You may register with us to use some of our member only features on our site. We may also offer the option for you to register with us without having to use any other product or service. During registration, you provide your "contact information" (which identifies you and how we can contact you, such as your name and email address) as well as certain demographic information (which describes certain information about you, such as your country of residence). You may be asked to enter a e-mail address and password. We may also ask you to provide additional information about your music preferences, so that we can cater to those preferences. The registration information that you provide will be reflected in the "My Hummaa" section of the service. 

* Communications with Friends. Our site may also have certain features that allow you to send information to others (such as via a "Dedicate a song"). We will use the contact information you enter for your friends only to send the email, and then we will delete it from our system. 

**Automatic Data Collection**

Copyright Tracking: In an effort to optimize our Site, Service and user experience, we may, from time to time, provide automatic updates, fixes or support, as we deem appropriate. Hummaa uses software that is designed to protect the copyrights associated with the tracks you listen to. In order to make sure that artists and copyright owners receive applicable royalties, this software identifies and counts the songs you have accessed. At the aggregate level (i.e., not tied to the personal information of any user), we use this data to report and pay royalties, for internal analysis and we share this data with certain Partners for their own analysis. We do not share your personal usage data with any third parties. We may use your personal usage data for a variety of Service-related purposes including, without limitation, for displaying advertising to users of the free ad-supported version of the Service. 

Cookies: We use what are commonly called cookies when you use our Service. We use these cookies to identify you as a valid registered user or subscriber so that we can deliver music to you, to ensure that no one else can sign on simultaneously with your account from another computer and to help us serve you better based on your registration preferences (such as your preferences with regard to what types of music you would like to receive). We may also use cookies to help us facilitate any promotions or surveys that we provide as well as the delivery of advertising to users of the free version of the Service. In addition, we may also use cookies in connection with a sign-in feature that allows you to save your email address and password each subsequent time you sign in and to track your use of free trial features. 

Performance tracking: We sometimes use cookies, as well as tracking technology, such as web beacons, within the promotional emails that we send to our registered user and subscribers or advertisements for our Site. Such information is non-personally identifying and collected on an aggregate level. We sometimes utilize third-party service providers to help us track the activity within our Site. These third parties may use temporary cookies and/or web beaconing technology to facilitate such tracking, but the data would not be tracked in a personally identifiable way. Third parties whose products or services are accessible or advertised on our Site may also use cookies, and we advise you to check their privacy policies for information about their cookies and other privacy practices. 

Other types of information collected: In order to better improve our Service, we capture other data such as a registered user's or subscriber's search criteria and results, date, time, connection speed and the IP address of each registered Service user, subscriber and Site visitor. We keep this information for our internal security audit log, aggregate trend analysis, and system administration. 

**When and with whom we may share your information with**

Other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy, we do not share your personal information with other companies. While we may use personal information (such as age, gender or personal usage data) to display advertising to registered users of the ad-supported version of the Service, we do not share personal information with our advertisers. 

Partners: If you access the Service through a Partner, we may share your registration information (such as your email address, year of birth, zip code and gender) with our Partner that you registered with for our Service. Vendors: We will share your personal information with companies acting as our agents in providing our service (e.g., customer/support services) to you, all of whom agree to use it only for such specified purposes. Each vendor must also agree to keep your personal information reasonably secure and confidential in accordance with applicable laws. 

Legally affiliated entities: In the event that Hummaa is merged, or in the event of a transfer of our assets, Site or operations, Hummaa may disclose or transfer your personal information in connection with such transaction. In the event of such a transfer, Hummaa will notify you via email or by posting a prominent notice on our Site for 30 days of any such change in ownership of Hummaa resulting in a change of control of your personal information. Legally compelled disclosure: We will also disclose your personal information when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena or other legal obligation, in response to a law enforcement agency's request, or in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing your personal information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (whether intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property. 

**Security**

Hummaa endeavors to protect the security of your personal information and your choices for its intended use. Although we will take (and require our third-party providers to take) commercially reasonable security precautions regarding your personal information collected from and stored on the Site, due to the open nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that any of your personal information stored on our servers, or transmitted to or from a user, will be free from unauthorized access, and we disclaim any liability for any theft or loss of, unauthorized access or damage to, or interception of any data or communications. By using the Site, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks. Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send any personal information to us by email. However, doing so is allowed, but at your own risk. We follow commercially reasonable security precautions to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during the transmission and once we receive it. Your Acceptance of this Privacy Policy: By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this Privacy Policy at any time so visitors are encouraged to review this Privacy Policy from time to time. Your continued use of our Site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes.

**Contact us:**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you can email us at [privacy-policy@hummaa.com](mailto:privacy-policy@hummaa.com)
